
  [{"question": "Who said That s what she said\" besides Michael?", "answer": "Dwight", "opt1": "Merideth", "opt2": "Phillys", "opt3": "Stanlley"},
  {"question": "What s Dwight s middle name?", "answer": "Kurt", "opt1": "Schrute", "opt2": "Howard", "opt3": "King"},
  {"question": "Who started the fire?", "answer": "Ryan", "opt1": "Andy", "opt2": "Jim", "opt3": "Dwight"},
  {"question": "When did Michael leave the show?", "answer": "Season 7", "opt1": "Season 6", "opt2": "Season 9", "opt3": "Season 8"},
  {"question": "Who was named regional manager after Michael left?", "answer": "Andy", "opt1": "Dwight", "opt2": "Creed", "opt3": "Robert"},
  {"question": "for how long Andy went on a boat trip?", "answer": "3 months", "opt1": "5 months", "opt2": "1 week", "opt3": "3 weeks"},
  {"question": "What is Erin s first name?", "answer": "Kelley", "opt1": "Sophie", "opt2": "Angela", "opt3": "Anne"},
  {"question": "What is the character that uses his real life name in the show?", "answer": "Creed", "opt1": "Ryan", "opt2": "Pamela", "opt3": "Angela"},
  {"question": "What does Jim send Dwight so he can identify office gays?", "answer": "Gaydar", "opt1": "Radar", "opt2": "Gay Radar", "opt3": "Metal Detector"},
  {"question": "What restaurant does Michael call thinking it is a hot juicy redhead?", "answer": "Wendy", "opt1": "Mendy", "opt2": "Sindy", "opt3": "Lenda"},
  {"question": "Where did andy graduate from?", "answer": "Cornell", "opt1": "Harverd", "opt2": "WG University", "opt3": ""},
  {"question": "What new employee is dubbed new Dwight?", "answer": "Clark", "opt1": "Pete", "opt2": "Plop", "opt3": "IT guy"},
  {"question": "What movie did Michael make?", "answer": "Threat Level Midnight", "opt1": "Threat Level Middway", "opt2": "Electric City", "opt3": "Two Lovers"},
  {"question": "Where did Scott burn his foot?", "answer": "GF Grill", "opt1": "The oven", "opt2": "The beach", "opt3": "his car"},
  {"question": "who did Kevin get on secret santa?", "answer": "Himself", "opt1": "Oscar", "opt2": "Meredith", "opt3": "Jim"},
  {"question": "how many lovers did Michael have on the show?", "answer": "4", "opt1": "2", "opt2": "3", "opt3": "1"},
  {"question": "Who is the office administrator?", "answer": "Pam", "opt1": "Oscar", "opt2": "Angela", "opt3": "Erin"},
  {"question": "what is the worst thinng about prison?", "answer": "The Dementors", "opt1": "The food", "opt2": "Loneliness", "opt3": "Criminals"},
  {"question": "What passport does Creed have?", "answer": "Swiss", "opt1": "Italian", "opt2": "American", "opt3": "Egyptian"}

]
